<tones>
  <tone>
    <name>Magnetic tone</name>
    <description>Attracting - Purpose - Unify</description>
    <explanation>Magnetics are the activators and the initiators of the wavespell and the powers of creation. You are an attractor of creative energy and power. You bring people together around you, catalyze movement and make things happen.</explanation>
  </tone>
  <tone>
    <name>Lunar tone</name>
    <description>Stabilizing - Challenge - Polarize</description>
    <explanation>The lunar tone knows that there is a delicate balance in the world that we are always walking a tightrope of wholeness and separation, of integration and release. Lunars can often be confrontational in the eyes of others, though you simply see it as a no nonsense way to be.</explanation>
  </tone>
  <tone>
    <name>Electric tone</name>
    <description>Bonding - Service - Activate</description>
    <explanation>You see connections and possibility where many don't, and then act on them. You are the current that electrifies situations. People who are electrics are often in careers of service to others, for you know the value of contribution to others and the long-term impact.</explanation>
  </tone>
  <tone>
    <name>Self-Existing tone</name>
    <description>Measuring - Form - Define</description>
    <explanation>Self-existings love to have details and know about measuring because they are always checking on how things are taking shape, what form they are taking. You are often meticulous and will plan, and make lists for any project or trip you are planning.</explanation>
  </tone>
  <tone>
    <name>Overtone tone</name>
    <description>Commanding - Radiance - Empower</description>
    <explanation>Overtones have an air of confidence about them which commands confidence, admiration and respect. Overtones, much to the frustration of others, are rarely wrong. That's only because you do your homework! You find it important to help people to become more than they are by bolstering confidence and esteem of others.</explanation>
  </tone>
  <tone>
    <name>Rhythmic tone</name>
    <description>Balancing - Equality - Organize</description>
    <explanation>Rhythmics are excellent thinkers and are very good at assessing a situation for the ideal outcome and weighing all of the options. You often think of activities that others do not, and so create new possibilities in their world for exploring new realms of thought and activity.</explanation>
  </tone>
  <tone>
    <name>Resonant tone</name>
    <description>Inspiring - Attunement - Channel</description>
    <explanation>You are an inspriation to others, your commitment and integrity are often models that others follow from your example. You are also a great cheering section for those you love. You are committed to your relationships and often desire to dive deeper into relatiosnhips and feel more connected to those you trust.</explanation>
  </tone>
  <tone>
    <name>Galactic tone</name>
    <description>Modeling - Integrity - Harmonize</description>
    <explanation>Galactics often model or hold the ideal of a paradigm that they explore. They rarely bend the rules, except when it will benefit others or a group, and are a shinning example of whatever vocation it is that you choose. You are very thorough in your research on a topic, and quickly become expert at whatever you focus on.</explanation>
  </tone>
  <tone>
    <name>Solar tone</name>
    <description>Realizing - Intention - Pulse</description>
    <explanation>Solars are always looking for something new to do, you are looking ahead and into the future. Solars can pulse a wondeful energy about them, it is as though anyone around you can bask in your confidence and quietude.</explanation>
  </tone>
  <tone>
    <name>Planetary tone</name>
    <description>Producing - Manifestation - Perfect</description>
    <explanation>You are a project finisher, a manifestor, and someone people can count on to get things done. Planetaries will be people who pay attention to details, all the way to the end of the task, then on to the next project, perhaps a breather afterwards, perhaps not.</explanation>
  </tone>
  <tone>
    <name>Spectral tone</name>
    <description>Releasing - Liberation - Dissolve</description>
    <explanation>The spectral tone knows the refined art of letting go and being present. You may lose track of time (not a bad thing!), because you are so present in your situation. Your type of personal organization is often a puzzle to those around you, don't let it bother you and don't let it bother them either!</explanation>
  </tone>
  <tone>
    <name>Crystal tone</name>
    <description>Universalizing - Coorperation - Dedicate</description>
    <explanation>You as a crystal, transduce energies so that we can all see that there is a universal meaning to everything. You are the keeper of the perrenial river of truth, and those who drink from it are your friends.</explanation>
  </tone>
  <tone>
    <name>Cosmic tone</name>
    <description>Trancending - Presence - Endure</description>
    <explanation>Cosmics have the patience of a great tree. Psychically, you have been thourhg most of what you experience around you, so you are often a good ear for others because of your enduring patience and perseverence. You can often see above the fray of emotional dramas, transcending the argument or conflict and offering calm, lucid, objective advice.</explanation>
  </tone>
</tones>